prismavps.com 2016-03-22

# Warpline $1 Web Hosting, $4 Reseller Accounts, $10 Domains, cPanel hosting powered by LiteSpeed!

This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect from you, what we do with the information, and our information security practices.

**Information**

When you sign up for our service, we will ask you to provide contact information such as your name, address, telephone numbers, e-mail addresses, and payment information such as credit card number and expiration date.

If you contact us for customer support, we may also ask you for information about your operating system, software and other technical matters. 

When you visit our Web site we will capture your IP Address, time of and duration of visit, and time and duration of the pages on our Web site that you view. We may tie this information to the personally identifiable information we have about you. 

We will also place a cookie that will identify you to us as a repeat visitor when you visit our Web site. See _“What is a Cookie”_ below. We may tie this cookie to the personally identifiable information we have about you. 

**Use of Personally Identifiable Information**

 ****

_We will use your personally identifiable information only as follows_ : 

• For payment purposes and to provide customer support; 

• To announce special offers or provide other information from time to time via e-mail. We may also send e-mail announcing special offers by our third parties, but we will not provide the third parties with your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information. If you do not wish to receive these e-mails, you may opt out of future e-mails at any time by following the instructions included in the e-mail.

• To improve our service and the marketing of our service. For example, we may use the information we gather from user surveys, demographic data, and web site visits to help us improve or target our Web site and customize your visit. 

_We will not provide any personally identifiable information about you to any other person other than_ : 

• a law enforcement or regulatory agency at their request; 

• Third parties who perform services on our behalf (such as payment processing), subject to the third party agreeing with us that it will keep your personally identifiable information confidential;

• As otherwise needed to protect or enforce or rights or the rights of others. 

**_We absolutely do not transfer or sell your information for inclusion on third party e-mail or other marketing lists._ **

**What is a Cookie**

A “cookie” is an alphanumeric identifier that is unique to your browser. The cookie will identify your browser to us when you visit our web site so that we may customize your visit. 

**Deletion of Data**

We respect your privacy. If you should decide to terminate your service with us, you may request all personal data be removed along with the termination of your account. 

**Changes to this Policy**

We reserve the right to change, modify, add, or remove any portion of this policy at any time. Any changes to our Privacy Policy be located at this address and will replace this version of our Policy. We may attempt to notify you of any policy changes. However, you automatically accept such changes by continuing use of our services.
